A Finding Aid to the 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. Records, 1939-2007, bulk 1970-2007, in the Archives of American Art AAA.55mercga
Archives of American Art
- Members and Guest Artists (Box 1)
  - Fintz, Jeanette R. - Fowlkes, Stephan, 1984-2004; undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Fintz, Jeanette R.
    Fowlkes, Stephan
  - Gardner, Joan, 1978-2006; undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Gennaro, Irene, undated; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Giersbach, Marilyn - Greenberg, Gloria, undated; circa 1980-circa 1998 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Giersbach, William
    Gifford, J. Nebraska
    Glovsky, Alan
    Goldberg, Gary
    Gordon, Dana
  - Gregg, Jon, 1983-1995; undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Handzel, Jane - Hochhausen, Bill, undated; circa 1981-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Handzel, Jane
    Heymann, Daniel
  - Honig, Ethelyn, 1973-1983; undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Huff, Anthony Leo, undated; circa 1981-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ingram, Lisa, undated; 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jessel, Robert - Louaver, Pierre, 1980-circa 2002; undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Jessel, Robert
    Karol, Diane
    Kuhr, Alexis
    Leggett, Liz
    Linder, Jean
    Linn, Judy
  - March, Stephen - Osnoff, Deborah, circa 1981-2001; undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    March, Stephen
    Millman, David
    Miss, Mary
    Mistal, Stanley
    Morriss, Annette
    Nozkowski, Thomas
    Oliver, Bobbie
    Osnoff, Deborah
  - Parlato, Carol - Schulte, Pete, 1980-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Parlato, Carol
    Parson, Charles
    Porter, Robert
    Robbins, Edward
    Schulte, Pete
  - Schuselka, Elfi - Shiihara, Tomatsu, circa 1982-1988; undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Scott, Aden
    Shiihara, Tomatsu
  - Simpson, Hester - Walker, Joy, circa 1980-2000; undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Simpson, Hester
    Strick, Racelle
    Swithenbank, Gail
    Thompson, Esme
    Tobias, Joel
    Tschinkel, Paul
    Von Rydingsvaard, Ursula
  - Wapner, Grace Bakst - Zempel, Jerilea, circa 1981 - circa 1985; undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Weinberger, Beatrice
    Wine, Gordon David
    Zempel, Jerilea